you've been tricked you've been betrayed
and you've possibly been bamboozled
we are back to the mansion but we are
not building the back of the mansion you
know i was hanging out here and i
thought about it you know i've just
swapped back with zeddaff right and i'm
back at the mansion so i thought ah
title of the video
perfect
back to the mansion but then i actually
got here and i was like do you know how
often
i come here only ever to joke about the
back of the mansion
i literally never ever
come here to do any work
anyway the back of the mansion is meant
to be made by scar at some point because
i won the turf war so
there's no point in me doing this and i
i haven't been back here in so long that
someone set up shop
i don't know why there's cows here
three diamonds i'm pretty sure this
wasn't me but i feel totally justified
in not working on the back of the
mansion because literally the only time
i ever come back here is to joke
that i haven't built the back of the
mansion but that is the title of the
video
because we are
back here and we are going to be doing a
little work i would really like to see
this project
get firmly completed and i'll be honest
with you there's not an awful lot left
to do in terms of the actual build
but there is a lot of work to do
here
and that's probably where i want to
focus my attention today
is getting some of this done now for
some reason this collection system likes
to just stop there's a bug where carts
just halt for some reason
when they're on a chunk border this is
it just messes up there's just some
weird bug and there's not a lot i can do
about it unless i want to make a new
system but you know what it doesn't even
matter because there's so many slime
balls and no one's actually buying slime
from the barge so
i am also not going to be doing
the same farm here because this is
producing more than i could ever need
but we'll come back to that later
because i do want to do a little bit of
work here possibly get some of this part
built and then we'll start to be able to
call
the mansion
relatively complete there is
ah there's remnants here might need to
swap this out again that's better
and there's one there as well zedf
really did make himself at home and we
might as well use our new fancy elevator
uh-oh
uh somehow i got pushed out of the
elevator that is so cool i saw a few
people saying that
we
i saw a few people saying that oh man
green and zed have swapped back so fast
you do realize we had swapped for like
four weeks we were in each other's bases
for a month that's quite a long time and
also i just want to point out i don't
want to swap forever
i did quite a lot at zf's space and he's
done quite a lot here at some point you
do need to swap back and four weeks
seems like an awful long time anyway i
think it's time that we crack on with
making this look a bit more presentable
than it currently does otherwise the end
of the season is gonna be hurtling
towards us and we're gonna leave some
things unfinished so let's hop into a
time lapse and get this thing built
[Music]
so i didn't manage to get a lot of the
detailing done that i said i would
however
it is at least
covered up
and not looking too bad there's still a
fair amount to do i need to add some
vegetation some trees but that's just
the case overall but we've got a basic
shell and i think this has made it a lot
nicer but what i have done is i've made
it not a very nice place
when it comes to mobs
yeah it's a bit of a mob heaven
see what i mean let's take a step back
and look at the overall effect now this
is probably going to annoy some people i
have made the mansion from day one very
symmetrical so everything that's on one
side is the same on the other now the
exception of course is the slime farm
which is there
because the slime farm is there
there's nothing on this side so it's
symmetrical
apart from that one bit so i don't i
don't think that's the end of the world
especially when the greenery gets put in
but overall we're starting to look
a lot more complete
than the start of the episode which is
really really good i can't wait to get
to the point where i can say yep i am
finished i've just noticed that
someone's come along and just
shaved the top of my birch trees this is
really odd
why would someone come along and just
take off the top layer anyway
i've had a message from our friendly
sewer cats telling me that it's time to
tot up the scores so what we're gonna do
now we're to fly over to cleo corrales
base and we're going to meet up with the
sewer cats which one of you
look to ender bro
you no no it wasn't me it wasn't looking
at him now
we can't get in the boat anymore because
there's a stinking skelly in there yeah
did you see what i i wrote
skelebro likes his personal space you
cannot get close to these guys because
they yeah no no
it's it's it's out officially out of
bounds um so i haven't been in the
sewers for a little while and it's now
chock full i'm not sure we could
actually fit much more in here so should
we do a point update yeah yeah i got a
lot going on guys you're forgetting your
cat heads
oh you don't want to yeah we go oh oh
he's got one now i lost mine
wow you lost yours i lost it with my
current skin i look like i'm here to do
your
taxes so who wants to go first show and
tell time right traditionally i will
start okay
right over this way what's the tradition
the tradition is i start
i like it so he started tradition now
yes today's the first day of that
forklift of course right that's that's
one thing i had before i also got one
two three four and five air conditioning
units nice from one of the buildings
and this light
the street light right here nice very
nice
big shine bank sign
from the bank nice
the best of all i took his entire wheat
field it's all
oh i love it yeah i love it you
harvested it okay okay all right okay
what do you got oh the oh okay we're not
deliberating on points yet okay yeah
let's let's see them i've done quite a
lot i've done quite a lot look i got the
most expensive rotten flesh and i tried
to frame b-dubs for it by putting his
head on in this place this is the this
is the rotten flesh i sold him for two
stacks of diamonds yeah
you like i thought you would like that i
also look at this this thing this
ambulance or whatever it is it's very
detailed i took that it took me quite
some time
and then looking around the corner over
here yeah we were running out of space i
had to tuck stuff in
look at this
nice
okay so i
i feel like i made the mistake of going
first because you guys knew exactly how
much do you mind
you guys knew exactly how much to to be
able to one-up me in a way so i kind of
revealed my because
i took this took this i took this crate
um
the um gas station sign or the petrol
station side these are cool uh and i
took this container and i took that tree
that was that was annoying to remake i
took a tree
so yeah i took a few bits but i feel
like i made the mistake of going first
to be honest with you yeah i knew
exactly what i needed to do to top you
yeah yeah scott what did you have you
you've done some bits and bobs apart
from that i have i have and to top you
all i have gone to the top of the city
to retrieve a plane
that's right we now have a
we've got
the south park mural should have started
with that one buddy
this is worth like maybe half a point
now
no it's a double sided because up on top
i replaced it with the sewer cats no you
guys don't want to be sewer cats anymore
but anyway the sewer caps up on the top
so double points right because brought
it down and
replaced the graffiti right above
i still think you should have led with
that one because you built an enormous
plane down here very yeah very wise yeah
it's all downhill from here
do we even need to tally points at this
point because did scott just win i feel
like it's pretty obvious
i think so i am dude good job buddy nice
imagination
that is audacious are you telling me
that no one noticed that that's gone
[Applause]
[Music]
oh no
well it was a fun game guys um very fun
it was very fun
it was crazy like we've been rumbled
well it was a matter of time we have um
run scar did it
it was scar
[Laughter]
well i think that might be the end of
that chapter we had a good run
and we got absolutely
busted now i did blame everyone but us
but um we didn't get away with it that's
that's the end of that now i did ask
corrales straight after that happened
does he want us
to put everything back and he explicitly
said no
don't touch anything he's going to
replace
the lighthouse but he genuinely he wants
the sewer he loves it he genuinely he
loves the sewer he doesn't want us to
touch it he doesn't want us to put
anything back which obviously massive
relief to me don't have to do anything
but he he loves it he loves the sewer he
thinks it looks amazing and he wants
everyone you know when the season ends
if they have the the world download he
wants everyone to like you know go and
enjoy it so he wants to keep it there
which
i have to agree i i think it looks
pretty cool but now that that's over
i'm feeling a little i'm going so fast
oh no i'm not i'm feeling a little bit
lost the base swap is done the corrales
base thing is done
i've hit the end of the road
quite literally but that's the great
thing about hermitcraft
over here we make our own fun
now my next project and i don't know
whether i'm going to start it today
is going to be barge hq
now scar actually messaged me saying
that he's willing to sell me this
property that i tried to get before i
left him signs oh he's right here he
said that i could have it at cost so i
don't even have to pay more he said i
can have it b dubs is here as well now
the reason that scar wants this isn't he
doesn't actually want the property he
just wants to get rid of this sign the
the billboard he wants to get rid of
b-dub's lovely face
why would you want to get rid of that
i see i see no problem here and and if
you go in here
there's something
there's a there's something about the
other side of this billboard that's just
hi there
so i can't wait to get my hands on this
property
and i can't wait to get my hands
on this because i have prepared a bunch
of blocks that i'm going to be using to
build up
barge tower
oh
he loves me
oh yeah he's there
he's just waiting for customers he bdubs
really wants to cut my hair but there's
no way i'm letting him touch
this fringe or my amazing waffle there
don't dead open inside
oh
don't open dead inside
just like my soul
why is everyone afk
just gonna take screenshots with all my
afk friends what is going on with scar's
face oh he's a hideous amalgamation of
mumbo and scar's face and night
independently
very handsome
put them together
not so much look there's mumbo's suit
and then there's scar's face and no this
is so wrong scar no please don't do this
what is this base swap done to you
you're never safe
you're never safe if you're afk
come on
scar you should know better
off we go
down we go
how far do you think we can push scar
before he realizes
he's okay i'm just taking my scar for a
walk
maybe i could get him into bdubs
barbershop
and we could give scar a haircut
walk-ins are available for the next 10
minutes
he's on his way it just takes a little
while here he is
got yourself
a fresh customer
he has no idea there we go come on on
the chair
on the chair
that's it he just right clicked he just
right clicked
he's
he back
oh he's back
he must be so confused this man
wants a
waffle in the back of his head like mine
you see he he wants he wants one of
these
one of these
why is that pete what's going on
i'm not sure what's happening anymore uh
this this was an afk prank i pushed scar
in here to get a haircut
and now we've got an audience
there's like there's six people outside
five people outside what is happening
and scars no
this didn't go the way i thought it
would i'll be honest this hasn't gone
the way i thought it would at all i
think i'm gonna leave
uh it's it's getting officially got a
bit weird i figured out what happened
there it after i left i tuned in to some
of the home whoa
i thought we were on a mushroom island
oh no we're going back i'm not getting
off this llama i am not leaving this
llama
okay so it turns out that i tuned in to
everyone's live stream and everyone was
using the proximity chat mod which is
kind of a new addition i haven't
actually played around with it myself
but i do want to give it a go which is
i think a really cool addition
but um i can't try it out because i'm
the only one on the server it's i'll be
honest
it's been a bit of a lonely ride i've
been on this llama
for about half an hour it's it's kind of
therapeutic to be honest with you the
only issue is
danger so what do you do
on the hermitcraft server when no one's
watching well i must admit not a lot and
not a lot i did find a few easter eggs
that i didn't know existed i was just i
was all wandering around having a little
mosey and i was like i bet there's
something in this
in this dumpster right and there is
it's my hopes and dreams
there's lots of little things like that
on the hermitcraft server but what there
is a lot of on the hermitcraft server is
profits in the barge and that's what i
want to take a look at so let's take a
look
see if we've got oh yeah we got some we
got some diamonds and it looks like my
stockpile of sand is also running out
i this is two hours worth of like
grinding for sand
and it's just gonna be gone again you
know what that's the first time i've
sold any barrels here's the thing i sell
chests and i sell barrels now they are
really expensive to make which is why it
costs two diamonds it costs like six
stacks of logs to make a full stack of
chests so this is really really
efficient way of purchasing them but
people would rather spend more
on the logs and then craft it themselves
but we have had a pretty good day on the
profit front at eight more diamond
blocks check that out i need to figure
out what we're gonna do with all of
these diamonds but i'll tell you
something else in the barge do you
remember barge quest all the way a few
episodes ago
first place prize
all of these boxes of goodies absolutely
everywhere i believe that scar and
b-dubs won but they haven't touched it i
don't know who this belongs to anymore
there's so much here that i'm tempted to
just stock up the barge they've probably
forgotten about it to be honest scar has
so many items i don't think he needs it
so my next task is probably to start
tackling a project that i've been
putting off for a while because of other
storylines going on but it is the barge
i want to focus on not restocking it i
mean you know there's not a lot of
shopping going on that those profits
that we just pulled out the barge are
probably like two weeks worth so it's
not an awful lot but i do want to do the
final expansion to the barge project but
it isn't going to just sell goods that's
what's really different about it it's
actually going to be
kind of a mini game um and i haven't
actually made any mini games this season
apart from like in the turf war so this
will be quite a unique project and i
think it will be quite a lot of fun and
of course we can uh upgrade the impulse
buys i mean this has been sitting here a
really long time i haven't checked
i think impulse has probably been
looking after it
so that's my next project for next
episode and of course building up barge
hq so it's going to be a bit of a barge
heavy episode next episode but while i'm
in the area i also want to check
if sedaf has done anything
to his base since i was here because the
thing is
the
the contraption that i made up above
here
well it didn't really work oh wow okay
he's done his own elevator
he loved the elevator so much he made
his own a chicken's life this thing here
it it didn't it didn't really work very
well there are some chickens there
i wonder if it's actually produced
anymore
it has i don't believe it i don't know
whether zed half has placed them here
himself
but there was 56 and now there's 64.
that is the most productive chicken farm
never that's that's the it's the worst
chicken farm ever and speaking of said
af
i feel like i need to give this another
go i i have a feeling that it's just
broken and won't work
but i just i just feel like i have to
give it that one more try i've just
realized that i've ended up resorting to
watching the clock tick on hermitcraft
at the moment
come on why is it always night when you
don't want it to be right we're gonna
have to just try this manually
here we go
well i managed to go through i don't
think this works i think zf has
generally genuinely just made a cow
killing machine
that's really unfortunate well that was
a little bit of a disappointing end to
the episode but i'm afraid that is all
we have time for today we did actually
get some stuff done today we have made
some more progress on the base and
unfortunately the cleo corrales games
have come to an end because we were
thoroughly thoroughly
busted
however i do want to say a huge thank
you for watching so far and i shall see
you in the next episode good
bye